Well, isn't this nice? In New York and
Brooklyn, um there are Muslims who are
patrolling Brooklyn neighborhoods in
what look like official police cars and
they're wearing official police
uniforms.
And the person in charge of this is
saying it's a neighborhood watch on
steroids.
Um and the Council on American Islamic
Relations said this is the first program
of its kind in the US and it needs to be
the last. So, they're patrolling saying
they're just, you know, asking people
how you're doing, blah blah blah. That's
not what they're doing. And this whole
group came to be because in 2017,
there were 14 biased incidents against
Muslims. So, this group was formed and
Mondami's turned them into basically
unofficial police.
Um
they want to expand this
over the entire city.
And I just found out what is being said
in those prayers that they broadcast
over like New York City. Um I think
Minnesota, Colorado I think is doing it
some and some other blue states. But
because it's in Arabic, we don't really
pay attention. We just think it's a
prayer. But here's what it says every
time and all day long.
Oh Allah, curse the Christians. They
call us oppressors. Curse the Jews. They
call them criminals. And curse the
unjust traitors.
Uh the people who have abandoned Islam.
Oh Allah, make them poor. Make their
lives miserable. Oh Allah, clothe them
in the clothes of misery and the
garments of calamity and make their life
full of pain and misery. Oh Allah, make
their lives full of misfortune and
afflictions and give them a tormenting
death. Oh Allah, fulfill your promise
and unleash your torment and pain upon
the Christians and the Jews.
And I was just going to read a few of
the
>> [clears throat]
>> quotes from the Quran.
3:28. Muslims must not take infidels as
friends. And that means non-Muslims.
5:33.
Maim and crucify the infidels if if they
criticize Islam. 8:12. Terrorize and
behead those who believe scriptures
other than the Quran.
>> [clears throat]
>> 8:60. Muslims must
muster all weapons to terrorize
infidels. And this just goes on and on.
And when you hear that we need them here
because they're, you know, they're so
cultural and and and we just need them.
Muslims are responsible responsible for
0.1%
of all scientific discoveries and
inventions. 0.1%
despite making up a quarter of the
world's population.
And they think that this the reason for
this
is we'll just say they like to marry
their cousins.